

Skills

Programming

Flutter
Dart
App
Publishment
Git
Skill
AWS
MongoDb
Firebase
SQL
Nodejs

Language

Türkçe English



MUSTAFA TURKMEN

FI UTTER DEVELOPER

Summary

I have been working with the Flutter Framework and Dart Language for over 5 years. I possess in-depth knowledge of web development stages, desktop, and mobile architectures. Additionally, I have remote working experience. I have volunteered for both local and national associations and charities. I have created educational materials and articles on technology and software. Learning new technologies and developing projects with them always excites me.

Experience

Mobile Developer

Algoritma | 2023 - Present Scooter Rent and Micro Mobility apps

Flutter Developer

Dusyeri | 2022 - 2023

Child focused / Mobile and / Web super app development

Flutter Developer

Guven Future | 2021 - 2022 Guven Hospital Official / Mobile and / Web app

Flutter Developer

Freelance

Flutter Application development / Desktop / Web / Mobile

Flutter Developer

SambaPos | 2020 - 2021

Mobile App Developer

Yesil Science | 2020 - 2021

Mobile Application Developing with Flutter Framework in Hobbycorn Product

Education

Computer Eng.

Harran University, Sanliurfa | 2016 - 2021

Contact

- ♠ Ankara
- **1** +90 (545) 414 9880
- ☑ iletisim@mustafatrkmn.com
- in seniorturkmen
- **y** @seniorturkmen
- @seniorturkmen

Projects

2024 **TAKSIM**

Bin Ulaşım ve Akıllı Şehir Teknolojileri A.Ş.

This app was fully written in Flutter within 2 months. The focus is on finding easy and safe taxis in Istanbul. The app has two sides: Passenger and Driver. I'm actively working on both sides in this project.

Web Site: https://taksim.digital

2023 GO-SHARING

Bin Ulaşım ve Akıllı Şehir Teknolojileri A.Ş. Sharing vehicle like e-scooter, e-moped exc. The app fully native written with Kotlin and Swift languages. I'm currently managing contact outsource connection and developing android side futures in this project. I'm also responsible for application release and update processes.

Web Site: https://tr.go-sharing.com/en/

2023 **BINBIN**

Bin Ulaşım ve Akıllı Şehir Teknolojileri A.Ş.

Electric Scooter Renting app fully rewritten with flutter

Web Site: https://www.binbin.tech

2022 **UPPY APP**

Dusyeri Software and Animation Corp.

Super app(include unity embeded games module(unity embeded & webgl), youtube module, book reader module, video player module)

video piayei module)

Web Site: https://uppyforkids.com/

2021 **ONEDOSE HEALTH**

Guven Future

BLe medical devices chronic disease tracking app made

with Flutter

Web Site: https://www.onedose.io/en/

2021 **GUVENONLINE**

Guven Future

Online treatment, online appointment application For

Güven Hospital made with Flutter

Web Site: https://www.guveninternational.com

Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=com.guvenfuture.mobile&gl=TR

IOS: https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/güven-

online/id1528965803?l=tr

Web App: https://online.guven.com.tr

2021 KIOSK DESKTOP APP

Desktop application for restourant kiosk machines made

with Flutter.

HOBBYCORN HOBBYCORN

Yesil Science

Hobby Based Social Media Application. made with Flutter

Android: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?

id=com.yesilscience.hobbycorn

IOS:https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/hobbycorn/id1537245

676

2020 TRACKER APP

Graduate Project

This app for follow your child when he/she is outdoors

made with Flutter

Github Link: https://github.com/SeniorTurkmen/Tracker

Volunteer work

ORGANIZER

Flutter Ankara | 2021 - 2023

Organizing event about Flutter Framework and bring the Flutter lovers together.

CO-FOUNDER

GDG-Sanliurfa | 2018 - 2020

The first GDG Chapter All Around the Eastern Turkey